WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
WJZ-TV Collection
1966-2000
Stage
R0129.WJZ
35 Linear Feet Mix of paper documents and still photographs
21,469 Cassettes
Mix of moving image formats
Scope and Contents
Consists primarily of local television news footage and local programing.
Historical Note
WJZ-TV Channel 13 is owned by the CBS Broadcasting, Inc. and is located in Baltimore, Maryland. The station was originally called WAAM and was Baltimore's third television station. When WAAM began broadcasting in November 1948 under the ownership of Ben and Herman Cohen, it was an ABC affiliate. In 1957, the Westinghouse Electric Corporation purchased the station and renamed it WJZ-TV.
In 1959, WJZ-TV built the first three-antenna candelabra tower, sharing it with the other local Baltimore stations, WMAR-TV and WBAL-TV. In 1977, WJZ-TV News began its Electronic News Gathering (ENG) Library, recording newscasts and retaining raw footage on a daily basis.
WJZ-TV often preempted ABC programming in favor of locally produced shows and syndicated content from Westinghouse's broadcasting division, Group W. The affiliation switch to CBS occurred in 1995, ending WJZ-TV's decades long link with ABC. Westinghouse bought CBS in 1996, making WJZ-TV a CBS owned and operated station.
Custodial History
The collection was donated to the University of Baltimore by WJZ-TV on August 16, 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is closed to the public while negotiations are underway with the donor regarding collection transfer.
- Afternoon, 1988; AFTRN; 13 Cassettes 3/4" U-Matic videocassettes
  Series Description
  Show dubs of a WJZ-produced television program.
  - Show Number One, WJZ-AFTRN-001-001 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 1)
  - Mom; Jewelry Rip Offs; Parenting Tips, 1988-08-10; WJZ-AFTRN-001-002 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 2)
  - Untitled, 1988-08-11; WJZ-AFTRN-001-003 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 3)
  - Number Five: How to Make Life Right; Bill Withers/Ken Hammond, 1988-08-12; WJZ-AFTRN-001-004 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 4)
  - Medical Waste; Retirement at 35; Jewelry of Israel, 1988-08-15; WJZ-AFTRN-001-005 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 5)
  - Emilio Estevez; Homer Formby; Fashions – The Limited, 1988-08-24; WJZ-AFTRN-001-006 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 6)
  - WFBR Radio, 1988-09-01; WJZ-AFTRN-001-007 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 7)
  - Harville Hendrix (Ph.D.); Wanda Geddie (Fashion Coordinator), 1988-09-15; WJZ-AFTRN-001-008 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 8)
  - (Master) Susan Lucci, 1988-10-13; WJZ-AFTRN-001-009 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 9)
  - Suzanne Somers & Susan Sunderland, 1988-10-19; WJZ-AFTRN-001-010 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 10)
  - Shirley MacClaine and Sandy Jones, 1988-10-21; WJZ-AFTRN-001-011 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 11)
  - Mamie Van Doren & Makeover, 1988-10-28; WJZ-AFTRN-001-012 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 12)
- Focal Point, 1966; FOCAL
- Get to Know, GTKNW; 32 Cassettes Betacam
- City Line, 1982-1989; CTYLN; 9 Reels Show dubs; edited masters 1" open reel video; 160 Cassettes Edited masters; masters 3/4" U-Matic videocassettes
  A public affairs television program with topics centered around the Baltimore City black community.
  - City Line, 1 Cassettes Video8, 60 minutes (Mixed materials 13)
  - City Line, 1 Reels 1 inch videotape, 5 minutes (Mixed materials 13)
    Scope and Contents
    KPIX5; aids; catholic vinette animation graphic; slow motion flag
  - City Line: Master, 1 Reels 1 inch videotape, 29 minutes (Mixed materials 13)
    Toni Morrison and her career and pulitzer prize wining novel beloved, Phyllis Hyman singing career, Don Williams exercise warm up tips
  - City Line: Master, 1 Reels 1 inch videotape, 5 minutes (Mixed materials 13)
    Opening tag
  - City Line: Master, 1 Reels 1200 feet 1/4 inch audio tape (Mixed materials 13)
  - City Line, 1 Cassettes Audio cassette, 90 minutes (Mixed materials 13)
  - City Line, 1 Cassettes Audio cassette, 120 minutes (Mixed materials 13)
  - City Line, 1 Files Computer print-outs (Mixed materials 13)
    CBS records management; magic me standup script
- Face Off, FACE; 1 Cassettes 30 minutes
  Local sports discussion program
- Evening Magazine, 1977-1991; EVMAG; 8 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 4,676 Cassettes
  During the summer of 1976, KPIX in San Francisco, a CBS affiliate owned by Westinghouse Broadcasting (Group W), premiered a local weeknight television news and entertainment series titled Evening: The MTWTF Show, eventually christened Evening Magazine. The show was designed to add a local focus to news. This show was created due to the FCC's newly enacted "Prime Time Access Rule" to give back the half-hour preceding primetime to local stations. The rule prohibited these stations from accepting network programming for that particular timeslot. This show was one of the first television news shows to begin the trend of shooting on videotape rather than 16mm film. The production called for the local hosts to have on-location wraparounds (in and around their local communities) and to tell short stories about ordinary and everyday people. As the show gained popularity, the other Group W owned stations around the country created their own Evening Magazine shows, including WJZ-TV in Baltimore. Evening Magazine was a locally produced prime-time access series that aired on the Group W stations in Baltimore, Boston, Philadelphia, Pittsburg and San Francisco. On other stations around the country the show was designated "PM Magazine".
  - PM Magazine, 1979-1990; 1755 Cassettes; 1 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad
    Another title for "Evening Magazine".
    - PM Magazine, 1985-08-27; WJZ-PMMAG-090-001 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 1)
      - Baseball's Oldest Pitcher., 1985-08-27; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 1)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-08-29; WJZ-PMMAG-090-002 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 2)
      - Crab Seasoning, 1985-08-29; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 2)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-08-29; WJZ-PMMAG-090-003 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 3)
      - Catamaran- Sailings Fastest Boat., 1985-08-29; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 3)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-07; WJZ-PMMAG-090-004 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 4)
      - Seduction Of Sports., 1985-09-07; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 4)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-16; WJZ-PMMAG-090-005 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 5)
      - Balto's Royal Affair., 1985-09-16; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 5)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-17; WJZ-PMMAG-090-006 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 6)
      - Llama Man., 1985-09-17; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 6)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-23; WJZ-PMMAG-090-007 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 7)
      - Cajun Cooking Invades New York., 1985-09-23; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 7)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-24; WJZ-PMMAG-090-008 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 8)
      - Tea Ambassadors., 1985-09-24; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 8)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-25; WJZ-PMMAG-090-009 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 9)
      - Baltimore's Beefcake., 1985-09-25; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 9)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-26; WJZ-PMMAG-090-010 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 10)
      - Surf Punks., 1985-09-26; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 10)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-27; WJZ-PMMAG-090-011 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 11)
      - Insult Clinic., 1985-09-27; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 11)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-30; WJZ-PMMAG-090-012 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 12)
      - Where Are They Now?, 1985-09-30; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 12)
    - PM Magazine, 1985-09-30; WJZ-PMMAG-090-013 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 13)
      - New Season (Anniversary Show), 1985-09-30; 1 (Mixed materials 90, Tape 13)
    - PM Magazine:, 1982-09-29-1982-09-30; WJZ-PMMAG-035-013 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 13)
      - Lady Shark Hunter, I Relived My Past Lives., 1982-09-29; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 13)
      - Nudist Convention, Dog Best Friend., 1982-09-30; 2 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 13)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-23-1983-08-24; WJZ-PMMAG-056-013 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 13)
      - Man Behind Twilight Zone, School For Snoops., 1983-08-23; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 13)
      - My Roommate Is A Computer, Pandemonium., 1983-08-24; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 13)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-19-1983-08-22; WJZ-PMMAG-056-012 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 12)
      - Balto. Lawyer To Holy Land Farmer, Death Defying Barefoot Water-skier., 1983-08-19; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 12)
      - Rocket's Dance Magic, 5 Mile Stilt Race., 1983-08-22; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 12)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-18; WJZ-PMMAG-056-011 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 11)
      - Death Nurse "Final Wish"., 1983-08-18; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 11)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-17-1983-08-18; WJZ-PMMAG-056-010 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 10)
      - Students Scared Strait, Live Mannequin Models., 1983-08-17; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 10)
      - I Make America's Hottest Commercials, Death Nurse., 1983-08-18; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 10)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-16; WJZ-PMMAG-056-009 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 9)
      - Teenage Homebuilders., 1983-08-16; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 9)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-11-1983-08-12; WJZ-PMMAG-056-007 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 7)
      - Smokey Is The Bandit, Lady Of The Bayou., 1983-08-11; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 7)
      - Dolly Parton's Double, We Have 27 Kids., 1983-08-12; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 7)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-09-1983-08-10; WJZ-PMMAG-056-006 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 6)
      - California Wildlife Rescue Squad, Healing Hands., 1983-08-09; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 6)
      - Snack Food Diet, Trendy Baby., 1983-08-10; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 6)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-04-1983-08-08; WJZ-PMMAG-056-005 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 5)
      - The Earth's Friendly Genius, Farewell To Tim White., 1983-08-04; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 5)
      - Heroic Escape From Death, Big Women Big Bucks, 1983-08-08; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 5)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-04; WJZ-PMMAG-056-004 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 4)
      - Farewell To Tim White., 1983-08-04; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 4)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-02-1983-08-03; WJZ-PMMAG-056-003 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 3)
      - Forest Park's Famous Grads, America's Freedom Border Patrol., 1983-08-03; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 3)
      - Basement Astronauts, Exercise Beats The Blues., 1983-08-02; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 3)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-03; WJZ-PMMAG-056-002 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 2)
      - Famous Forest Park Grads., 1983-08-03; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 2)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-02; WJZ-PMMAG-056-001 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 1)
      - Basement Astronauts., 1983-08-02; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 1)
    - PM Magazine, 1983-08-15-1983-08-16; WJZ-PMMAG-056-008 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 8)
      - Celebrity Party Crasher, Magnificent Men In Their Flying Machine., 1983-08-15; 1 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 8)
      - Grandma's $25,000 Shopping Spree, Teenage Home Builders., 1983-08-16; 2 (Mixed materials 56, Tape 8)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-08-31; WJZ-PMMAG-034-001 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 1)
      - The Toughest Colt: Coach Frank., 1982-08-31; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 1)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-01-1982-09-02; WJZ-PMMAG-034-002 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 2)
      - Space Camp For Kids, Women Racers., 1982-09-01; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 2)
      - Skydiving Dogs, Shock Trauma For Kids., 1982-09-02; 2 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 2)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-03-1982-09-06; WJZ-PMMAG-034-003 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 3)
      - Hollywood Monster Maker, The Go-Go's., 1982-09-03; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 3)
      - Lawyer For The Little Guy, We Have 27 kids., 1982-09-06; 2 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 3)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-06; WJZ-PMMAG-034-005 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 5)
      - We Have 27 Kids., 1982-09-06; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 5)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-07; WJZ-PMMAG-034-006 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 6)
      - Truckers Rodeo., 1982-09-07; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 6)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-07-1982-09-09; WJZ-PMMAG-034-007 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 7)
      - Tom Selleck Look-Alikes, Truckers Rodeo., 1982-09-07; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 7)
      - I'm The Lindberg Baby, Empire Strike's Back On Radio., 1982-09-09; 2 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 7)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-10; WJZ-PMMAG-034-008 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 8)
      - Tim Topper., 1982-09-10; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 8)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-12-1982-09-13; WJZ-PMMAG-034-009 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 9)
      - Wing Walker Marilyn Beck, Brook Shield/Prince Albert, Sky View OF Balto. Excuse Booth, Videotape Interviewing., 1982-09-12; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 9)
      - Mr. T, Chef Tell, Olympic Underwear Model Original Storm Master, Guy Who Sails Single-handed, Horoscopes-Buffalo., 1982-09-13; 2 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 9)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-13; WJZ-PMMAG-034-010 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 10)
      - Doctor Of The Aquarium., 1982-09-13; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 10)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-14; WJZ-PMMAG-034-011 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 11)
      - French + Indian War., 1982-09-14; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 11)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-14-1982-09-15; WJZ-PMMAG-034-013 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 13)
      - Chef Tell's Good Life, Refighting The French + Indian War., 1982-09-14; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 13)
      - Balto's Dracula, Littlest Majorette., 1982-09-15; 2 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 13)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-15; WJZ-PMMAG-034-014 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 14)
      - Baltimore's Dracula., 1982-09-15; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 14)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-15; WJZ-PMMAG-034-015 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 15)
      - Littlest Majorette, 1982-09-15; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 15)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-16; WJZ-PMMAG-034-016 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 16)
      - Doug Marlette – Ace Cartoonist., 1982-09-16; 1 (Mixed materials 34, Tape 16)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-16-1982-09-17; WJZ-PMMAG-035-001 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 1)
      - Bad River Suicide Horse Race, Ace Cartoonist Doug Marlette., 1982-09-16; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 1)
      - Searching, For Real ET's, Lottery Instant Millionaire., 1982-09-17; 2 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 1)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-20; WJZ-PMMAG-035-002 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 2)
      - Baltimore Screen Painting., 1982-09-20; 1; 1 Cassettes 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Mixed materials 35, Tape 2)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-20; WJZ-PMMAG-035-003 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 3)
      - Window Street Art., 1982-09-20; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 3)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-20; WJZ-PMMAG-035-004 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 4)
      - King Of The Sandcastles., 1982-09-20; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 4)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-22-1982-09-23; WJZ-PMMAG-035-005 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 5)
      - What Your Nightmares Mean, King Of The Sandcastles., 1982-09-22; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 5)
      - TV's Topcat Morris, Act Heroes., 1982-09-23; 2 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 5)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-23; WJZ-PMMAG-035-006 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 6)
      - Team Of Heroes., 1982-09-23; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 6)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-24; WJZ-PMMAG-035-007 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 7)
      - Museum of Broadcasting, 1982-09-24; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 7)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-24-1982-09-27; WJZ-PMMAG-035-008 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 8)
      - Unknown Title, 1982-09-24; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 8)
      - Unknown Title, 1982-09-27; 2 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 8)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-27; WJZ-PMMAG-035-009 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 9)
      - She Bosses The Big Guys., 1982-09-27; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 9)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-28; WJZ-PMMAG-035-010 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 10)
      - Spray-Paint Masters., 1982-09-28; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 10)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-28; WJZ-PMMAG-035-011 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 11)
      - Spray-Paint Masters, Las Vegas Magic w/ Tigers., 1982-09-28; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 11)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-29; WJZ-PMMAG-035-012 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 12)
      - Lady Shark Hunter., 1982-09-29; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 12)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-30; WJZ-PMMAG-035-014 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 14)
      - Nudist Camp., 1982-09-30; 1 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 14)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-02-1981-12-03; WJZ-PMMAG-017-001 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 1)
      - My Life Is A Comic Strip, Bob Smith: Speed Demon., 1981-12-02; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 1)
      - Skyward Suzy's Career Soaps, A Potato Chip Is Born., 1981-12-03; 2 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 1)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-04; WJZ-PMMAG-017-002 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 2)
      - Meet Jaclyn Smith, Water Squirrel., 1981-12-04; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 2)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-07; WJZ-PMMAG-017-003 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 3)
      - My Incredible Gorilla Family, Million Dollar Hands., 1981-12-07; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 3)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-08; WJZ-PMMAG-017-004 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 4)
      - Basement Inventor Becomes A Celebrity, I Write Racy Romances., 1981-12-08; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 4)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-08; WJZ-PMMAG-017-005 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 5)
      - Basement Inventor Becomes A Celebrity, I Write Racy Romances., 1981-12-08; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 5)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-08; WJZ-PMMAG-017-006 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 6)
      - Basement Inventor Becomes A Celebrity., 1981-12-08; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 6)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-09; WJZ-PMMAG-017-007 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 7)
      - Consumer Revenge., 1981-12-09; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 7)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-09-1981-12-10; WJZ-PMMAG-017-008 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 8)
      - Consumer Revenge, Tammy Wynette's Soap Opera Life., 1981-12-09; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 8)
      - TV's Most Hated Women, Your Personality & Your Dog., 1981-12-10; 2 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 8)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-11-1981-12-14; WJZ-PMMAG-017-009 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 9)
      - Preppy Power, We Have 200 Xmas Trees., 1981-12-11; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 9)
      - Mom & Marie Osmond, Hometown Treasures (Bottles)., 1981-12-14; 2 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 9)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-14; WJZ-PMMAG-017-010 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 10)
      - Hometown Treasures., 1981-12-14; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 10)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-15-1981-12-16; WJZ-PMMAG-017-011 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 11)
      - Kathy's Courageous Comeback, Chesapeake Ice Boating., 1981-12-15; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 11)
      - We Make You Bulletproof, Ebony Fashion Fair., 1981-12-16; 2 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 11)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-17-1981-12-18; WJZ-PMMAG-017-012 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 12)
      - Soap Opera Digest, Santa Of The Appalachians., 1981-12-17; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 12)
      - Wind Walking Superman, Flea Market Bonanza., 1981-12-18; 2 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 12)
    - PM Magazine, 1981-12-21-1981-12-22; WJZ-PMMAG-017-013 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 13)
      - World's Largest Xmas Tree, You Can Quit Smoking., 1981-12-21; 1 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 13)
      - BJ. Thomas Inspiring Comeback, Animals-Angels OF Mercy., 1981-12-22; 2 (Mixed materials 17, Tape 13)
    - PM Magazine, 1982-09-20; WJZ-PMMAG-035-002 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1990-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-175-006 (Mixed materials 175, Tape 6)
    - Sister Mercy: Sports Casting Nun #6, 1990-01-11; 1 (Mixed materials 175, Tape 6)
    - Evening Magazine: January 15, 16, 18, and 19, 1990, 1990-01-15-1990-01-19; WJZ-EVMAG-175-004 (Mixed materials 175, Tape 4)
      - Mrs. Filbert's Margarine, Hazel Mills Diaz., 1990-01-15; 1 (Mixed materials 175, Tape 4)
      - John Fairchild., 1990-01-16; 2 (Mixed materials 175, Tape 4)
      - Holland-Dozier-Holland, The Hidden Files., 1990-01-18; 3 (Mixed materials 175, Tape 4)
      - Mayor In A Mess., 1990-01-19; 4 (Mixed materials 175, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-08-29; WJZ-EVMAG-001-001 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 1)
    - Ponies of Chincoteague(1), 1977-08-29; WJZ-EVMAG-001-001-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-08-29; WJZ-EVMAG-001-002 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 2)
    - Ponies of Chincoteague(2), 1977-08-29; WJZ-EVMAG-001-002-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-08-30; WJZ-EVMAG-001-003 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 3)
    - Mercy on Southern, 1977-08-30; WJZ-EVMAG-001-003-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 3, Segment 1)
    - Ali on Southern, 1977-08-30; WJZ-EVMAG-001-003-02 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 3, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-01-03; WJZ-EVMAG-008-016 (Mixed materials 8, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-001-004 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 4)
    - Dolly Parton(1), 1977-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-001-004-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-008-014 (Mixed materials 8, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-001-005 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 5)
    - Dolly Parton(2), 1977-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-001-005-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-20; WJZ-EVMAG-008-012 (Mixed materials 8, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-01; WJZ-EVMAG-001-006 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 6)
    - Want to Lend a Band, 1977-09-01; WJZ-EVMAG-001-006-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-29; WJZ-EVMAG-008-011 (Mixed materials 8, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-02; WJZ-EVMAG-001-007 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 7)
    - Evening Show #5, 1977-09-02; WJZ-EVMAG-001-007-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-008-007 (Mixed materials 8, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-02-1977-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-001-008 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 8)
    - Architect Loves Baltimore, 1977-09-02; WJZ-EVMAG-001-008-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 8, Segment 1)
    - Street Savior, 1977-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-001-008-02 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 8, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-08; 1 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 15)
    - J. Anderson on Washington, 1977-09-08; WJZ-EVMAG-001-015-001 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 15, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-08; WJZ-EVMAG-002-001 (Mixed materials 2, Tape 1)
    - Moonrise Still Shrines, 1977-09-08; WJZ-EVMAG-002-001-001 (Mixed materials 2, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-16; WJZ-EVMAG-008-006 (Mixed materials 8, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-05-1977-10-03; WJZ-EVMAG-001-009 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 9)
    - Fly Solo, 1977-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-001-009-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 9, Segment 1)
    - Brooks Last Summer, 1977-10-03; WJZ-EVMAG-001-009-02 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 9, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-15; WJZ-EVMAG-008-003 (Mixed materials 8, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-05-1977-10-07; WJZ-EVMAG-001-010 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 10)
    - Brooks Last Summer, 1977-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-001-010-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 10, Segment 1)
      - The Van Man, 1977-10-07; WJZ-EVMAG-001-010-02 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 10, Segment 2)
    - The Van Man, 1977-10-07; WJZ-EVMAG-001-010-02 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 10, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-09; WJZ-EVMAG-007-017 (Mixed materials 7, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-001-011 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 11)
    - Evening Magazine, 197-09-05; WJZ-EVMAG-001-011-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-08; WJZ-EVMAG-007-015 (Mixed materials 7, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-06-1977-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-001-012 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 12)
    - Lip Service, 1977-09-07; WJZ-EVMAG-001-012-01 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 12, Segment 1)
    - Fighting my Way Out, 1977-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-001-012-02 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 12, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-12-05; WJZ-EVMAG-007-012 (Mixed materials 7, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1977-09-07-1977-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-001-013 (Mixed materials 1, Tape 13)